<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Server on Aamon&#39;s site</title>
    <link>http://aamon.xyz/tags/server/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Server on Aamon&#39;s site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Aamon Magnusson - 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:49:01 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://aamon.xyz/tags/server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Server Update</title>
      <link>http://aamon.xyz/posts/server-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:49:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aamon.xyz/posts/server-update/</guid>
      <description>As can be read from my Hugo Setup and Nextcloud posts, currently my site is running off of a Raspberry Pi 4. It is still proving to be a great low power server, with fairly good performance. It&amp;rsquo;s not like it should replace dedicated servers, but I like it for what I need.
I am now running a couple new services, which I will go through in the post. In total I am running the following (in order of installation):</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;As can be read from my &lt;a href=&#34;http://aamon.xyz/posts/hugosetup/&#34;&gt;Hugo Setup&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://aamon.xyz/posts/nextcloud/&#34;&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/a&gt; posts, currently my site is running off of a Raspberry Pi 4.
It is still proving to be a great low power server, with fairly good performance.
It&amp;rsquo;s not like it should replace dedicated servers, but I like it for what I need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am now running a couple new services, which I will go through in the post.
In total I am running the following (in order of installation):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Apache&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;PiVPN&lt;/code&gt; (&lt;code&gt;Wireguard&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also have some future plans of other things to host, and run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;apache&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Apache&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not much has changed about the &lt;code&gt;Apache&lt;/code&gt; running.
I did try to setup certificates, but that ended up breaking the installation, which caused me to re-image the Pi entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have the port open to make the site accessible from the internet, and that&amp;rsquo;s about all for fancy configuration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;nextcloud&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The installation instructions from &lt;a href=&#34;http://aamon.xyz/posts/nextcloud/&#34;&gt;my Nextcloud post&lt;/a&gt; worked great again when I had to reinstall &lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Past that not much has changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;pi-hole&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/code&gt; is a &lt;code&gt;DNS&lt;/code&gt; ad-blocker.
I use it on my entire home network, as the default &lt;code&gt;DNS&lt;/code&gt; server.
(That is set in my router)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not perfect, and I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would recommend it.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t work on YouTube ads, and messes with the sponsored links from google.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;rsquo;m running it now, so I might as well keep it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The installation is super simple.
Run the &amp;ldquo;One-Step automated install&amp;rdquo; from their GitHub:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;curl -sSL https://install.pi-hole.net | bash
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow the instructions, and make the needed changes to your router.
(If you want it to be the default &lt;code&gt;DNS&lt;/code&gt; server)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fixes&#34;&gt;Fixes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a couple things that might need fixing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I first set it up ads were still showing up on my Windows machine, that can be fixed by disabling IPv6 on the machine.
Instead of doing that I disabled it for the entire network, in my router.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through a few weeks of use I noticed my YouTube watched history was not working.
Turns out there are several domains that will get blocked that are needed for some small function in several sites and services.
The list of known domains that may be needed can be found &lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.pi-hole.net/t/commonly-whitelisted-domains/212&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
To fix my particular issue run I ran the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;pihole -w s.youtube.com
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;pihole -w video-stats.l.google.com
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;pivpn&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;PiVPN&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;PiVPN&lt;/code&gt; is simply an installer for either &lt;code&gt;Wireguard&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;OpenVPN&lt;/code&gt;.
Either of which will allow you to &lt;code&gt;VPN&lt;/code&gt; into the network from which the device is hosting the service is from.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am using it as a method to access some things that are within my network, but not accessible from the internet.
Like my &lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt; instance, and to access my Raspberry Pi and Kali machines through &lt;code&gt;ssh&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This also means I can work from home, from anywhere.
Some things I do with work are linked to my IP, which I am able to use through the VPN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation-1&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similar to &lt;code&gt;Pi-hole&lt;/code&gt;, the install is done through one command, and some guided questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;curl -L https://install.pivpn.io | bash
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there you will also have to open a port on your router, which will depend on the service you use, and if you change the port during install.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;Wireguard&lt;/code&gt; apps are super easy to use, and seem really quick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;plans&#34;&gt;Plans&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have several services I would like to add, and some clean up I need to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First on my list, I would like to get a reverse proxy/tunnel set up with CloudFlare.
I&amp;rsquo;m hoping this will be an easy way to secure any services I want open to the internet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next I would like to set up an app like Memo, for taking quick notes.
I currently use Google Keep, but self-hosting would be good.
Plus it would be Markdown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Not that I think I will self-host it, but I would like an email server.
I&amp;rsquo;m thinking I will use AWS SES, due to the complexity of self-hosting.
This will be used for the next service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m thinking I would like my own password manager.
I&amp;rsquo;m leaning towards Bitwarden, but that is not final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Past this are just potentially cool things that I might do someday, but not soon, like a Matrix server, so that I can have my own chat room, and an RSS feed collector.
Oh, and I could also run a Minecraft server, for the &lt;em&gt;lols&lt;/em&gt;.
These will be a fair bit further out though.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nextcloud</title>
      <link>http://aamon.xyz/posts/nextcloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 11:18:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aamon.xyz/posts/nextcloud/</guid>
      <description>As should already be known, I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this site off of my Raspberry Pi 4. Since my goal with is it to make it the best server for myself that I can, it is now running my own Nextcloud instance.
Nextcloud is an open open-source alternative to Google Drive, OneDrive, or Dropbox. As with the other services, you can pay for cloud hosted access, which makes it feel like all the other cloud shares.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;As should already be known, I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this site off of my Raspberry Pi 4.
Since my goal with is it to make it the best server &lt;strong&gt;for myself&lt;/strong&gt; that I can, it is now running my own &lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt; instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt; is an open open-source alternative to Google Drive, OneDrive, or Dropbox.
As with the other services, you can pay for cloud hosted access, which makes it feel like all the other cloud shares.
(While being open-source, which is still cool)
What makes &lt;code&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/code&gt; special is that you can also self host your own instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have a few options for hosting:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Docker&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;Snap&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VM image&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I initially tried to get the all-in-one &lt;code&gt;Docker&lt;/code&gt; image working, as I&amp;rsquo;ve had a little experience with &lt;code&gt;Docker&lt;/code&gt; from building a &lt;code&gt;CTF&lt;/code&gt; in work.
For what ever reason copy pasting the command from the Github didn&amp;rsquo;t work, even though it was the &amp;ldquo;Command for arm64 CPUs like the Raspberry Pi 4&amp;rdquo;.
I found that fairly strange, as &lt;code&gt;Docker&lt;/code&gt; and other container systems are meant to make running programs work on whatever system.
Whatever, I just decided to run the &lt;code&gt;Snap&lt;/code&gt; which seems like the preferred method by Linux users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past I&amp;rsquo;ve not been a fan of &lt;code&gt;Snap&lt;/code&gt;, but when I think about it as a &lt;code&gt;Docker&lt;/code&gt; replacement I&amp;rsquo;m more of a fan already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To get an instance running with &lt;code&gt;Snap&lt;/code&gt; you only need to run one command:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo snap install nextcloud
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is really cool!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I have some more specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t have it running on port 80, as that&amp;rsquo;s where the &lt;code&gt;apache2&lt;/code&gt; server is running.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I want to have all the data running on an external drive, so that it does not impact the system storage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While these sound specific, they are not difficult to setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First I had to set an environment variable.
&lt;code&gt;$SNAP_COMMON&lt;/code&gt; is the variable that controls where the data goes.
To set it for all users creating a file in &lt;code&gt;/etc/profile.d&lt;/code&gt; with the export will do it.
I created a file called &lt;code&gt;nextCloud.sh&lt;/code&gt; and wrote the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;export SNAP_COMMON&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;/media/aamonm/Small&lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;\ &lt;/span&gt;Drive
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;And for the other requirements I ran the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo snap connect nextcloud:removable-media
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo snap connect nextcloud:network-observe
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;sudo snap set nextcloud ports.http&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;81&lt;/span&gt; ports.https&lt;span style=&#34;color:#f92672&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:#ae81ff&#34;&gt;444&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other than that, I opened my browser to &lt;a href=&#34;http://aamonserver:81&#34;&gt;aamonserver:81&lt;/a&gt; and completed the setup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I now have my own &lt;em&gt;cloud&lt;/em&gt; share, so that&amp;rsquo;s pretty cool, and useful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is only accessible from inside my home network at the moment (Same as the site itself)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I have not set up certificates, since I can&amp;rsquo;t do that on port 81 or 444, which is where I want it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Setup</title>
      <link>http://aamon.xyz/posts/hugosetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 19:16:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://aamon.xyz/posts/hugosetup/</guid>
      <description>This site is written using the Hugo framework. As written on their website:
Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators. With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again.
Thus far, I find those statements to be true. By the number of themes I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to find, it does seem popular. It is most definitely fast, and is fairly flexible (for what I have the skill to do this thus far).</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This site is written using the &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; framework.
As written on their &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators.
With its amazing speed and flexibility, Hugo makes building websites fun again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus far, I find those statements to be true.
By the number of themes I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to find, it does seem popular.
It is most definitely fast, and is fairly flexible (for what I have the skill to do this thus far).
And for the first time ever, I &lt;em&gt;might&lt;/em&gt; be having some fun writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ok, so the guide of how I&amp;rsquo;ve set up this site.
I don&amp;rsquo;t plan on doing a step by step guide on how to use &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt;, however the things I think are special will be mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the actual &lt;code&gt;Hugo&lt;/code&gt; stuff, I&amp;rsquo;m using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/panr/hugo-theme-terminal&#34;&gt;Terminal&lt;/a&gt; theme, written by &lt;code&gt;panr&lt;/code&gt;, which I have as a git sub module.
I guess that reminds me, this is in a git repo, so that I can edit from any device.
(It is private right now, we&amp;rsquo;ll see if that changes)
The &lt;code&gt;config.toml&lt;/code&gt; contents were copied over from &lt;code&gt;panr&lt;/code&gt;&amp;rsquo;s Github repo, so that I have all the configuration options.
Changes clearly had to be made to make it mine, which is not hard.
I then ran:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new about.md
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new showcase.md
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new _index.md
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;And started filling the site with some content.
Like to make this post:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#272822;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;hugo new posts/hugoSetup.md
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where I find it gets more interesting (can you tell I&amp;rsquo;m not a web dev?)	is how I have the site running in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m (at least currently) hosting this site locally off of my Raspberry Pi 4.
Nice and light weight ARM machine, that I currently don&amp;rsquo;t have too many uses for.
(I do want to self host &lt;code&gt;NextCloud&lt;/code&gt; as well, stay tuned)
I connect to the Pi through ssh, which I set a static IP within my LAN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To actually broadcast the site, I&amp;rsquo;m running &lt;code&gt;apache2&lt;/code&gt;, the tried and true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the static IP makes it easy enough to access the site within my network, I was able to also set a local Domain Name, through my router&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;DNS Host Mapping&amp;rdquo; setting.
This makes it feel like that much more of a website, at least to me&amp;hellip;
Within my WiFi network&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have also set up port forwarding to make the site accessible everywhere on the Internet.
This was much easier than expected, going into the &amp;ldquo;Port Forwarding&amp;rdquo; setting in my router.
I also purchased my own domain name, so this site can be viewed from &lt;a href=&#34;http://aamon.xyz&#34;&gt;aamon.xyz&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I plan on getting a cron job working to update the site to whatever is pushed up to my &lt;code&gt;Github&lt;/code&gt;, but so far I have not been able to make that work.
Will show my steps to that at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
