<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aamon&#39;s site</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aamon&#39;s site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Aamon Magnusson</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 12:31:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://example.com/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 12:28:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/showcase/</guid>
      <description>This page will showcase some things that I have done or made that I am proud of. Not all are technical, just whatever comes to mind.
DWM I have spent a fairly significant amount of time setting up my DWM config, which can be found on Github. Through it I have taken the time to learn Git, patching, bash scripting, and customization within the FOSS space. While DWM is window manager, I have created a desktop environment, to an extent.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;This page will showcase some things that I have done or made that I am proud of.
Not all are technical, just whatever comes to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;dwm&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;DWM&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have spent a fairly significant amount of time setting up my &lt;code&gt;DWM&lt;/code&gt; config, which can be found on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Aamon-Magnusson/AamonDwm&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.
Through it I have taken the time to learn Git, patching, bash scripting, and customization within the FOSS space.
While &lt;code&gt;DWM&lt;/code&gt; is window manager, I have created a desktop environment, to an extent.
Nearly everything that I need to make a bare Arch Linux install usable is installed through one script.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By no means is this impressive to many people, or really impressive at all, I am just proud of the work I&amp;rsquo;ve put into my Linux desktop through &lt;code&gt;DWM&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Aamon-Magnusson/AamonDwm/master/GeneralView.png&#34; alt=&#34;DWM screenshot&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;+++&amp;gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:41:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
I&amp;rsquo;m Aamon.
I work as a cyber security analyst. Within that I work as a pentester, SOC analyst, and what ever else I&amp;rsquo;m given.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also gained an interest into Gnu/Linux (That is that last time I will add the Gnu on this site), and open source software. I&amp;rsquo;ve grown to love the customization, and terminal use, that much FOSS software provides. With that I use Neovim, and DWM as my main preferred pieces of software.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Hello,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Aamon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I work as a cyber security analyst.
Within that I work as a pentester, SOC analyst, and what ever else I&amp;rsquo;m given.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve also gained an interest into Gnu/Linux (That is that last time I will add the Gnu on this site), and open source software.
I&amp;rsquo;ve grown to love the customization, and terminal use, that much FOSS software provides.
With that I use &lt;code&gt;Neovim&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;DWM&lt;/code&gt; as my main preferred pieces of software.
(I will likely try to write something about my preferred workflow)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am also familiar with Windows.
(Thanks Microsoft for not making that optional :|)
&lt;code&gt;Powertoys&lt;/code&gt; is an amazing collection of software to make Windows that much more usable.
(Also it&amp;rsquo;s FOSS :))&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside of tech, I love riding, and working on bikes.
I currently own 5 bikes, ranging from a fixed gear, to an IBIS Ripmo AF (Full suspension mountain bike).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this site I will write about whatever I decide to.
Some may be guides for things that I know, or that I just learned.
This will help me ingrain the skills I have and learn.
Others may be recipes that I want to keep a hold of.
But in total this is largely to get me to write, which is far from one of my highlighted skills.
I tend to think of myself as a technical person, and this may help me branch out of that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I doubt many will get even here, but thanks for reading, and please reach out to give any guidance or recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
